I'd like to introduce you to this brand
new horror, the flesh thing. And
honestly, I have no idea how somebody
came up with this. Now, you may know
that one issue with computation is the
ability to have true randomness, to have
nonlinear thought to control complex
systems. A human arm, for example, is
too complicated for traditional AI to
operate. There's just too many small
moving parts. And one solution was using
the tiny human brains that we can
literally grow in jars if you want to.
Or you can create AI that behaves like
them. And that's exactly what
researchers did when they created this
flesh tentacle Eldrich horror. Each one
of those muscle fibrous arms are
controlled by an individual virtual
brain organoid. You can even see them
floating there for some reason.
Flesh systems, soft systems require
something that resembles real
randomness. Linear thought just isn't
enough. So you have to introduce
nonlinear thought, which our brains do
excel at. In a way, our brains operate
like quantum computers. They are the
most complicated computer that exists on
Earth. We just, you know, use them to
look at pictures of cats on the internet
and other things. This may be the next
frontier to creating artificial systems
that are truly intelligent. Yes.
Biohybrids are an option, but our flesh
is flawed. It requires oxygen, it
requires nutrients, and it can degrade a
necro. Along with creating nanobots that
can selfheal, we may bypass the need for
biology at all. While I always say that
we should borrow from nature, I never
said we should plagiarize it. Frankly,
when we strictly plagiarize, we get a
lot of things wrong. We create things
that rot. So, why not create something
similar? something that doesn't interact
with the environment, something that's
not susceptible to infection. And yes, a
lot of people do mention mirror life,
but I don't think it's truly as
dangerous as it's made out to be. Like
I've told you, viruses don't have rules.
They have all kinds of different
nucleotides that we don't have. But we
still have immune systems that are
designed for randomness, to meet new
challenges and destroy them. Even if you
created mirror robots, they would still
suffer the same consequences. things
would figure out how to degrade them.
But when we're talking about things like
plastic, bacteria are just getting a
hold of how to degrade it. Even wood,
which at one point was on this planet
and critters had no ability to digest
it. They eventually figured it out, but
wood is still pretty sturdy. Even though
your home may eventually decay, you can
still build a home out of wood. It's not
easy to degrade. Ultimately, I want to
see robots with the same ideas. things
that look very much like biological
systems, things that think like our
brains but are not susceptible to the
same things we are. I want to create
something better. I want humanity to
create something that could actually go
out into the stars and long survive us.
I don't want to make humans immortal. I
would be much happier to pass on the
torch to something else. So, what do you
think? It's a flesh thing just to start.
Do you think we'll create something
better or annihilate ourselves